{
    "id": "a8e277d198dd4138b0fd9777e6fb61f3",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The book ………………… you gave me was interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c8cda1170a9e40aeb0462360070672f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ………………….. stood first in our class is my friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "722330ccf6ca4de589bd680f9a9b4044"
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me the books …………………. you borrowed from my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d0ddbe0bfbd44b3491c5c156bc46f0b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know the man ...................... daughter won the first rank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ccea1dfd1dff41489fc5c9ac74f8d8f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "John is the guy ...................... helped me when I was in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb3fb8fe705747dbb3b201a998f804a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I consoled the man …………………. wife had been killed in the accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who's",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba7c6369bea747c0b0546a1be91bf161"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plants ………………… grow on the mountains look lovely.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "who",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da2acb5da5be4fb7801179744cf1b2a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the only story in this book ………………….. is worth reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50efb344062246dcbf508794de0ce6df"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw a girl ………………….. beauty took my breath away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8406de79a38e4dfd90b3e2560951a844"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ...................... I spoke to is my classmate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5b659bf9ec04f5cb9ea5801fe6e7202"
        }
    ]
}